Check, check, same search.
Freshers smoke you don't bring facts you bring light and you don't tell truth
You cast roles and you pick the wrong
For me
You build a case out of side eyes, thumbnails and tone
Turn a rumor to a rally, put it up on a throne
Take a dozen loose fragments, stitch a monster from scraps
Then you point at your creation, like, see, I'm just stating facts
Now you bait with suggestion, let implication do flips
Got a mouth full of poison and a courtroom eclipse
Everything's a pattern when you need that crowd fed
You sell fear and a sermon with a live stream
The nation approved with guilt by association cheap
Deep, bad faith, crack, day-long.
First comes the grand theory, then the caskets are signed.
Then you act like you got X-ray vision straight into my mind.
Everybody's a puppet, everybody's in play.
Till the facts hit the room and your mystique melts away.
You call paranoia wisdom, call projection a gift.
Float a charge, then dim the light
Let the audience connect the dots
While you act shocked at what they got
I'm just asking question sure
With a loaded wink and a poison slur
I'm just noticing a trend
Yeah, every witch hunts as that in the end
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Thanks for coming back. It's okay. It was just your thumb. I look I had a second look at it
It wasn't a penis that it was it was your finger now
You know what my my favorite part about the AI songs is that I write to myself actually
Just like just when you think your fucking suffering is about to end they
Well, oh my gosh cute. Oh my god. I lost them. Oh, there he is. He's back. I'm so sorry
They come right back
Just like you
Just like you Q okay
Don't sit there and pretend like you don't fucking like when I join your panels fucking
I know you wish I know I do I want it I want that fix six
You have it one time just one time just one time there's one time for everything, right?
Don't leave don't leave on down buddy. It's okay calm down. I'll shut up. I'm shutting up. Oh, we have another guess
No guns. If you show your gun, you are banned forever. Okay. He's got weed. What is that?
Cheeto. Oh, this is your boyfriend
My boyfriend my boyfriend is Squidward. This is six boyfriend. Oh, okay, my bad. Yeah
Signal is my boyfriend. Okay, but what about can you cut are you gonna come with your wife?
Make me tacos enchiladas and that have sex with me. What's your video tapes?
as long as you pay for the rancher I mean
Deal that a deal. It's deal. It's $15
Deal, okay sealed seal with a kiss got it
What the fuck are you eating Cheetos flaming hot? Yeah. No, those are like
Puffy ones a puppy flaming hot bro them shit's look wet
Yeah, I put I put hot sauce and I knew it Mexicans put hot sauce on the flaming hot
Yeah, cuz they're just speed-running death
Hot sauce and lemon. Oh my god speed run heart disease
Actually, I'm actually healthy mother fucker. I know you look real healthy
You look like a fucking you look like the fucking symbol of health
I'm gonna get up here and turn a globe keep your Glock
I could I could around the cop
Hey from LA. I heard only fucking pussies are from LA
Psyche
We know you're a pussy. I
Don't have a pussy, but and I won't eat one, but I'll put my finger
Why does this rule got Matt? Why he got Matt cuz I don't know. I don't know who's that
Jealous, he's jealous. I know he's Joe here. Hey, you're jelly. Mr. Mr. Big Peppers will say you're jelly of me
You're jelly.
I can't believe me.
Me and Psyche.
Me and Psyche are gonna have a fucking freak out.
Yeah.
Hey, Amber.
This is the closest I'm getting to sex in probably my life.
It probably won't ever happen,
but it's the closest I'm going to get to it.
So I got a lot of months.
Okay.
He's not, he promised you're not going to fill out the gun
or a porno, right?
You promise?
No, no, no, no, no.
Let me see your wife's hand.
Oh, you're cat look at the cat look at the cat look at my face. I mean look at my signees on my cat
She used to as a heater
We are signees if you please we're like twins. We're like he's like my mexican brother with from another mother
Oh madre as they say
Inside he lived five minutes away from each other. We do. Why aren't you at my house yet?
You come tonight if you want
Cuz you don't buy my you don't buy my favorite cigarettes. I'll buy I'll buy your favorite cigarettes
What's your favorite cigarette bread? I'll buy them right now. I'll walk to the 7-11
Where are they tonight not tonight? Okay. No, no, no, no, no shade a no shade. No, no shade
In the money on a in the money on a how about we have a whole day together now. We'll make it a content
We will
Amen, and he made an amber. Come on. Come on
You mean me?
Little porn bombs and shows guns. I want to see your can you show me your muscles?
And I wasn't for people porn bombing and showing guns. We wouldn't have any content around here guys guys
All I have is either talk about
And talk about guns and porn bombs, okay, just give me a break give me a fucking break guys
Okay, I think everybody we should just all go to rumble where we can look at my camera
It's very looking at the camera. Yeah, my kids. She hears my voice and I'm like I'm like a doctor do little
Right
Cuz you know why cuz I do little work. Hey Sharon, what's up sweetheart? That's up sweetheart. Hold on Sharon
I don't care if you're like
I like Dr. Dick little a psyche and let's they hit me up on my Instagram
So we could set it up for the stream. We're decided for the stream
Sharon, I'm gonna remodeling out Sharon and I don't care if you're Alex's spy or whatever because I like Sharon just because you know
Exactly, my Instagram is 300 underscore glow, I'll do it right now.
I'll do it right now.
Yes.
Let me do it right now. So I don't forget. I'm gonna do it right now. And then I'm gonna watch it up the stream
That should be crazy. It will be great guys. This will be where you're the pier
Get jealous. We're gonna have people it will be so jealous. Jelly. They'll be jelly about 300
I'm sorry. Okay. I got you. No, it's wrong. It's
Roam on this court 300
Roam or n
Yeah, wrong
Okay, let me look let me look I'm the skirt 300
Okay
Oh, it's always go, right?
Okay, I followed you. Okay. I request I requested your friendship. Okay
Okay
There's made this stream happen. It should happen. I'm good. Okay
But Sharon, she like fucking gay guys and his friends list
We're gonna be LA niggas and they're gonna be hating on us. Yeah, they need
Man, nobody hating on you bitch. I'm in San Bernardino. You'd be scared to come out here
You'd be scared to come out. You'd be scared to come out the same Bernardino boy
You wouldn't even come out the car you'd be scared to come out the way
I want to go to that's it
Be scared to hop out the way
San Bernardino doesn't even have burger. You be scared to hop out the whip. It's okay, buddy
It's okay. You live in the middle of nowhere, bro
I'm gonna tell you that if you think that the Inland Empire is the middle of nowhere, then you're crazy
You've never been to the middle you've never been to the middle of nowhere
The Inland Empire there's 200,000 people in San Bernardino it ain't the middle of nowhere
Oh, there's 2,000 people where I live and they all hate you
I'm sorry, but I tried to make it right. No, it's retarded
Okay, I just loop it with no camera
Okay, he's fine. He's fine. He's fine. He's fine. I think you got no camera. I'm trying to touch you
He'll go on camera. He'll go on camera. He was on camera tonight
Okay. Oh, you don't know me. Do you boy? Yeah, I don't know you bitch. Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh
Hold during low. He's this guy's famous. Hi
Set up to this famous
Yeah famous. Yeah
Deliberty shut up to you. He's a legend. He's a legend. He's cute. Just think it's the
Sucker I love his hair
Love it here. Hey through your glow tomorrow. I'll suck your dick if you come over. All right, okay
I'm gonna buy my cigarettes in my Wii right? Yeah, of course
You have to come over Friday
Read the weed tomorrow bring the weed I'll buy you a cigarette. He wants you to be Jen's ducky
Too late my boy
Too late you're already Jen or he's mine
Yeah, it's too late. Uh-oh. Oh, okay. He left now. I can fall asleep comfortably
But Q you know how to sing Q?
They probably just accidentally left. I know. Yeah, do you know how to sing a song?
Do you see me? Yeah, I can sing a song for you. Sing a song to the chat in me.
Whatever you want to say.
No, there's no N words. There's no one where it's involved.
And you're fucking insane mate
I think you need a doctor's appointment
It might send you to the shrink
Or maybe that's what you fucking need mate
Blah blah blah
So watch your neck and shut your mouth up
You were nothing but a little stupid fucking slut
So shut your mouth
You fall down south. I might remove a few teeth of from your mouth mate
Shut your fucking mouth mate. What is that song?
You were such a fucking state. I don't like the song. I don't like the song. Stop it. Stop. I can't fall asleep to this
Can you please stop singing that
Thank you so much
Thank you so much. You asked me to sing a song. I know but then he's it was it's hard to get violent and scary
It's it's the song that El made made one day. Oh, if you ever met a mate
He's a British dude. Oh, yeah, I met him. I met him for sure. He was on the show the other night. He's Crunchy's e-boyfriend.
Oh no, I hate Crunchy.
Crunchy is more like, like, Crunchy is like more like, like, like, like kind of a moist, dross of flake.
Not Crunchy, kind of like, Crunchy is a retard.
She I call I'll call her soggy from now on. She's soggy
You you're my friend and I thank you for being here. I don't know me weird, but you're my friend. Oh
Do you want to hug?
Can I have one?
No, I'll get on the train. I'll take the hour train ride down to the beach. I'll give you a hug in person, buddy
But not you're not gonna kill me, right?
I've never killed anybody before yet
But would you would you like hug me so hard that I my back breaks and I I'm a pair per legic
Wouldn't take much
Well, please don't do that. I don't want then if we can't come over
Yo, what's up, what's up with this dude?
This is my here's this gay guy. Yeah, it might be so what you bro. You're straight
So you're taking advantage of psyche of being gay or what was wrong with you?
I'm gonna take advantage of you. You're pretending to be gay, bro. That's what's true
I think I'll force you down spit in your booty hole. Oh my god
So you're forcing people so I'm making me tell you cute. I thought you were gonna do that to me
You know why you know why I'd spend your booty hole. Why?
because in prison they consider that a rape because there's human body fluid in
another person. When they put like a whole packet of this of the honey or
syrup in the butthole and then eat it out. What's that called? A pancake in prison?
A prison pancake? So you know what after you do that you're gonna get
You're me, but I mean a nice wear and then your mom's gonna get
Fuck I didn't expect him to say
He came out of nowhere
He's not coming over you. What the fuck. Well, you know, he's like he's crazy. So, you know
You can't. Come on. Listen, you know this community. People are going to go crazy. Come on.
I know, but not like, fucking, like, like, insane, like, they're certifiably, like,
put them in the solitary confinement in prison and throw away the key type crazies, you know?
Well, maybe they are.
Yeah, I think so.
I mean, he is. He is.
And if you're gonna glow I will cut open your fat belly with a like a gutting knife of a fish
Okay, and then I'll suck out your intestines
And then I'll tie them around your neck and I will hang you from me put me hook for saying that okay
That's not how you speak. That's not how you talk to the Mexicans
You say I'm gonna get the fucking chunk let that out and I'm gonna
I mean I said I said fish the hook knife. I meant the chunk let that okay
Okay, okay, okay, okay. All Mexicans are scared of the chunk let that yeah, okay
And I have a chunk let that okay. I have one and the next song will be you should have two of them I
Have actually four but the next song will be three hundred logo gets the chunk let that and then
I'll I'm gonna steal his wife and she's gonna make me into the artist. That's the song. Okay, okay
And we're gonna laugh. We're just gonna laugh at him
We're gonna laugh for the rest of her make it like that. I bet his wife probably looks like Shrek. I
Don't care if she as long as she makes good enchiladas. Have you heard bitch?
Never make a pretty woman your life. Oh, maybe she looks like Fiona
I'm not bad. I don't care what she looks like because you make enchiladas is the only song I have I
Want I just want that or no, I don't know my only requirement. I just need
enchiladas with the verde sauce and like I mean she made him a plate of a food the other night
It looked like this
Somebody once told me the world was gonna roll me
And Nathan talked to me, and I ain't the sharpest tool in that shed
Sorry, I thought it was a duet
She was looking kind of dumb with her finger in her thumb on the shape of an L on her forehead
Well, go ahead using it
It's okay Q, you know what?
Well, they got me thinking about they got me thinking about 300 glows wife
Which got me thinking about Shrek with guts got me thinking about fucking that song. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's a great song
I love that movie, but Q. I mean, it's like hey, we're having fun and it's like it's like it's like bros
I would never even like
Give you a hug and then try to touch your butt. I promise. I swear to God. I might do it
Wait, what is the amber thing? Do you think his wife is better looking than who me? Amber. Well
Amber, can you make enchiladas?
Because Amber I'm gonna be honest with you
I've seen men that I'm more attracted to than you. It's not about like how attractive you are
It's how good are your enchiladas? That's my requirement. Look how I'm about to die of starvation
If someone can come over and make me a plate of enchiladas and like
I bet 300 glues wife got two butts one in the front and the back
That's called a what's it called a moose knuckle or something and moose knuckle
Spread it like foodie beauty
Foodie beauty foodie beauty is not come on stop it
It was that is that Benny in your picture that looks like Benny a little bit. I didn't know you gained so much weight
That's not Benny. Who do you think that is?
That's not beta it's not beta no
Is it obviously not be there that you and you were like
Turned 18 or something. I don't know you're closed
It's a foopa. Yeah foopa. No, it's my fucking dad when he was like 20 something. No, it looks like you
It looks like you okay. It looks like you
It's like that's why I said you're close when you say it look like me. Yeah, that's my dad when he was like
I have a good eye. I have a good eye. I have a good eye, but it looks like every 25 in the 80s
It's you after you ate a lot of enchiladas and stuff.
It's actually your dad.
You know, it's weird the older that I get.
Like when I was younger, everybody's like,
oh, you look just like your mom, this and that.
The older that I get,
the more I'm starting to look like my dad though.
You know what I mean?
It's like, it's weird.
You got your hair from him.
You got the hair, you got that like a memcana.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I got my hair from him.
You've never seen a picture of my mom before.
My mom was just fucking hairs.
You both got, maybe, but you have that like,
that mean look from him.
When you get mad and stuff, you have that mean look.
You know, like, I have that, it's like,
cause people say, oh, you're always a mad.
And I'm like, when I'm like just like looking normal,
I'm like, this is my normal face.
I have to like kind of like really like,
kind of like, I had to do a lot of muscles
to look kind of nicer, but my normal face is like this.
It's my normal face amber. That's amber. I don't I don't think like I don't know what you're trying to say there
She says oh, I don't think she I don't think he realizes how similar his genes are to mine
Yeah, but the thing is amber. I'm a dude, so I'm like supposed to look like this
You're a girl. You're not really supposed to look like a dude
They're saying
No, don't I'm going to do if I want to flirt with my guests. He can like tell me he's gonna gut me like a fish himself
And he's told me that several times
With a chiklata chiklata a
Chanklata I'm glad that hey your family my family junior East Coast to actually my family actually found in Harlem
That's why I can say the n-word
They're from the Netherlands and they've founded Harlem Harlem is a town in the Netherlands
HR I think that you should spout the n-word as much as possible because it will
Desensitize people and they just stop caring. That's what happened with me
If I said the n-word right now nobody would give a flick because I said it a million times
Well, he does know but just don't don't remind them because I don't want him to like beat me up or mace me or anything
I like this guy
I don't want it to with the hot sauce. Don't hit me with the hot sauce, please a pepper spray. Maybe
You're not the hot sauce
No, that's what the hot sauce is. Oh
Okay
That's what I mean by hot sauce
Yeah, don't hit me with the hot sauce, please. I
Saw a cue mace himself on the street on his own stream probably how much that was fair mace
$500 or what $500 or $300 250?
Okay, I would do I would shave my head for 250 and a half of one or less
And if I could go back and
You always died you almost died you couldn't breathe. I wouldn't need if I would need a thousand thousand
I mean, yeah, that was like 250 that now he had they got into the bargain price
I'm I was literally the most that was the worst like pain though
Like I was literally crying for the ambulance because you can't breathe when that shits all over your face. You're like
My sister, my little sister, we were looking for a lot.
She found my dad's mace when I was like probably seven.
She was probably five years old
and she like thought I looked so dumb reading my book.
And she just, she thought she was macing the book,
but she maced me when I was like literally seven years old.
And that was like, I still remember that was like
the worst pain I think I've ever experienced in my life.
And so I-
Okay, so imagine that, imagine that like-
It's five thousand ten.
Five thousand ten.
times. Yeah. Yeah. Like you've been you've seen what my face looked like. You see what my face
looked like. It was bad. I've never seen that shade of red in my life. It was bad, bro. And then
and then I fucking and then you get into the shower to try to like clean it off and it runs down
to your dick. And then your dick hurts, right? Oh, your dick doesn't just hurt. It was so bad
to the point where I couldn't sleep with a blanket on me because the weight of the of just a little
What hurt me ouch ouch guys I have one more sip and I had to sleep with two air conditioners pointed at me like it
Dude, it was a nightmare. It was so bad
There I can still like you know how usually like when something happens to you like you forget the pain of it
Like you don't remember exactly how bad it felt. You know when it's been turned I still fucking remember vividly
Well, that's why you know that was that was a year ago. That was that was 11 months ago
And even I still I still fucking remember a little motion you let me play that clip and stuff and you were like nice about it
Because I didn't ask for permission, but you didn't like I was told like I talked to Q
And he said he wasn't gonna strike you for that and stuff. I appreciate. Oh, yeah, cuz it technically wasn't my clip
I did it on crack it on a stream, but I I said I told him like yet to let you play it
So not cuz he was I we me and him had an agreement at a certain point whenever we made that clip like
You know if any basically this was for Sam man if Sam man or anybody else in that part and that little community were to play
We were gonna strike them down, but I was like, you know, we can make an exception for certain
We're not gonna strike everybody, you know
You are definitely a legend cuz that like someone's just said the base best base I've ever seen yeah
You're not gonna find a better someone macing them in the face than that clip. I think that is forever
I don't think anybody would ever do be crazy enough to do that again
But it's like that that was like you get it to yourself
I mean you you base yourself in the faith your face turned like this shade of red that was like
Like some kind of death poison and it's like and it's like that was impressive. It really was you're a legend
I remember before I did it crack it on I was like oh
If you can make it like an if you can make it like five minutes or something without any water or milk or anything
I'll give you more money or whatever. I couldn't even make it 30 seconds
That's how bad it was like I couldn't even dude psyche. I don't I can't even it's I can't even describe to you the feeling of it
It's so bad. It's literally feels like your skin is fucking melting off your face
It's so bad. I mean, it's meant to it's meant to stop a bear, you know, it's meant to stop a fucking bear
That was bear mace my dad had this little can of like a mason stuff like that. It was like in the 80s
It was probably like a lot less
and but I was seven years old and it was like shot at the book but I was like I just remember that
I still remember how bad that was so it must have been you times like you know a hundred
thousand whatever and then like what a lot of people don't take into account also is the fact
that like so the the bear maze can has like a high psi like it comes out fucking fast you know and
You know what I'm saying? It comes out like, it's like a pirate thing with your mace.
I mean, you put it right up to your face. Like, seriously, guys, if it was like,
it literally had, it literally had a recoil like a gun. Like I had to hold it steady because it
like recoiled back into my hand. You know what I mean? Like this shit like kicks up.
But the funny thing is like, you like took like three deep breaths. Like you didn't
like postpone them for like 20 minutes. You just like took three breaths and then you did.
I knew.
I knew if I postponed it, I was gonna pussy out and I wouldn't do it.
I had to just fucking, you know, just nut up or shut up right then and there.
And Sharon, I just wanna have Sharon real quick, Sharon's in the shot.
I'm sorry if, like, is she, like, has she turned against you?
I know I'm not on her list because she won't even say my name,
but I, like, I don't know.
I don't want to cause any problems with you and her and stuff.
Hopefully you guys are still cool, but it's like,
she hates me so viscerally much.
I've never seen her with anybody say,
I won't even say that person's name,
but I'm gonna make some memes of him, of him, bald.
You know, I mean, she's, I hope you're okay, Sharon, okay?
Just, you know, I don't know, I don't know Sharon.
I can't even, I can't put it in words right now.
I'm a little bit upset, but not with you,
but you know, with stuff that's just going on,
but Sharon is cool as fuck.
Sharon's cool as fuck.
Hey, Rudy, you wanna come over here
and cut it with a little bit?
Look at this cat, look at this cat.
You know how old this cat is, Q?
You see this cat right here?
Do you, Rudy?
A-Q.
What is your age, seven?
He's 18 years old.
18 holy sure I got him last year because she was moving and she's like I have a cat
He's like 15 and she dropped him off. She's like he's like, I think he's maybe 18 and
He's like a little old man and it's like I
Don't know how long will have you know how long he'll I hope he lasts till like 25 30 years old
Like I just hope he lasts as long as possible
But he's like a little old man now, but he's like a very sweet cat
He hid under the bed for like over a month
And now he, like, comes and finally he's a cuddler
under the blanket with me.
Like, it's like, well, he won't go out of the way under.
He just, like, puts his butt under it
and, like, puts his head out of it.
But he's a little sweet, and he's very, very soft.
He's a sweetheart.
Yeah.
Amber. No, I don't care what others think.
I just don't want you sign it.
And, yeah, I don't know, she's, okay, she signed an NDA.
Okay, oh, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Yeah, I don't care what others think.
I think she's, but it's like, no, she's seriously,
I can't even talk about it right now,
what she's doing to me behind the scenes.
But she's doing some shit behind the scenes
that you would all say that's fucking fucked up.
And it's like, she's doing it and she doesn't care.
But I can't say what it is, but we'll talk later.
We'll talk later, privately, yeah.
My kiddies don't really know anything besides me.
Yeah, I know. Well, you're they're like cute seriously
And that's why I like you as like a cat dad and stuff because you know tricks was born here
I got Lola and Lenore when they were like they were like little street cats
Like they were just running around the street as kittens. I got them both as kittens
But look like Lola when I got Lola, I was like
Okay, I said I can't take another cat as they please don't let me look at her
He brought her in a little carrier. He's like I just bet and rushing this cat off the sidewalk up, you know
And I can bad part of town
And I was like, and then he, I was like, please,
I was like, please don't even let me look at her.
Cause I can't have another cat.
I think I had five cats at the time.
And he's like, well, can I go run to the store?
I'll be back in 10 minutes.
I was like, okay, in 10 minutes it passed.
And then I like, I was like, well, he's probably not coming back.
I opened the thing.
She came out and she had all these boogers in her eyes and stuff.
And I like got a fleek home and I like wiped out all the boogers,
like really, really gently.
And she opened her eyes and she has these green,
like the most beautiful green eyes I've ever seen of a cat.
And I was like, okay, this cat is mine.
And she's like so sweet.
See, when I lift the covers,
she just jumps under the covers with me.
Like, she jumps under and then she goes,
and all my cats are like, they jump under the covers,
they go, they're purring like a motor.
I'm probably not gonna sleep with that,
probably a human ever again,
but I have my cats to like...
you know, keep me warm and stuff and like so I'm a happy person, you know
I'm a lucky blessed person and
You know, that's it. It's like it's like the cats are my family. My loves my my life and you know
These little animals used to fucking sleep with me all the time until I discovered the window
Now all they want to do is sit in the fucking window all the time
Well because they because that's like well, can they go outside and stuff?
Yeah, I let them outside once in a while, maybe like a couple, maybe two or three times
a week they go outside, but they're always like supervised, they don't.
Yeah, I put it I have a little I have a like kind of like I have a small backyard
But there's like you know
It's like kind of like the city is kind of like very quiet city
And so I and I didn't like just having to go down open the door and like and then worry about like having it open
And stuff because I've got these weirdos coming so I just like I got a cat cat
I have a cat flap at the door so they can come in and out as they want
But these cats and so and some cats have run away because of that but
These cats they always come back. They always like you and it's like it's just the best having these cats
You know, I'm living like an apartment complex. That's like has it's like all the doors lead into a courtyard
Yeah, I mean so I just they just kind of play in the courtyard and then eventually when I want to go inside
I just like grab them up and put them back in the house
And you know Rudy was a hunter like she said oh, you know Rudy like used to get this big rat and then he would
I look under my pool table and she's like and the rats guts were just all spread out under there
and he just tore it apart and
Like one night Rudy came back and he got a mouse and then like I looked the next day and the mouse was just
He just tore the mouse apart and he was so proud and it sounds disgusting
but it's like I was like so proud of him because
You know, he's still like, it's like,
imagine like an 85-year-old man that was-
Amber can pretend like she don't like me,
but, you know, she don't, she might not love me,
but she definitely don't hate me.
That's for sure.
I'll say, like a lot of people I think like hate me.
It's like, remember when Marty died
and then Cyrax was like, oh, he just picked his death.
And then the next day, he's like, Marty.
because like sometimes your nemesis is actually like some kind of like energy
source or it's like you each feed each other in a certain way and it's like when
they're gone it's like eight years Marty eight years Marty
You like to roam channels and show love?
Yeah, and I'm glad, hey, Sharon, I'm really glad,
and I haven't seen you on her channel
because I do watch her once in a while,
but I'm really, because I know she's like,
she banned Gotti, she banned Jamie's Cowboys,
she bans Mermaid, she bans all these people,
they're even like going to my chat and stuff,
so I hope that you're okay, like she's okay
with you being here because, you know,
I don't want you to be in any trouble
because of me and stuff, I would feel really bad.
because I didn't see that's the gay that's gay that I am gay I'm gay okay I'm gay okay no not
not not the homosexual type of gay I'm talking about the like corny type of gay like that's the
issue with the community I don't care I don't care okay who bans on AM I can't say her name right
now it's just AM I can't even it can't get her name out of my mouth right now it's just AM I'll
You go look at her community post go look at your community post Sharon. I don't know if you've seen them. There's at least
15 I think 10 to 15 memes of me
With a like bald head like you know trying to pick up young boys
In a fire. I mean, it's like the sickest shit. I've ever seen in my life
I think it's funny at the end of the day because it's like it's just so out of
This world like you know ridiculous, but at the same time she's doing fucked up shit to be behind the scenes
I can't talk about right now
I'll just say she's doing some fucked up shit that is like way out of any kind of like I mean if she was just doing that
That's bad enough. She's doing some fucking fucked up shit
And you know what she'll face her karma for that too, but
I just hope you don't face any consequences for for just even like being friendly and stuff, you know
So like you you're just it's not getting through your head
I don't know how many times I have to say it to you like nobody takes Alex seriously
You just need to laugh at this. It's just a good. She's a goofball. Well, do you take beta seriously?
No, okay, so it goes into this so neither do I but at the same time
I loved these people from the ball of my heart
and it's like I will have an affection for them.
and if it sounds corny, if it sounds gay,
if it sounds whatever, I will still have an affection
for them, probably for the rest of my life.
I will never get over it because when my,
I'm a Capricorn, Capricorns when they bond,
because they don't bond with many people.
When they bond.
You need to learn to adjust,
because you can't, if you're gonna be on here,
like you're gonna come across a lot of people
that you're gonna like one day
and then one day you're gonna not like them.
You know, but I really don't,
I mean, I'll say horrible things and stuff back.
but i really don't hate anybody hey are you like you're just starting out like you're still kind
of beginning i know are you in areas or areas or a tourist what's your sign i'm a Pisces okay
okay your Pisces do you have blue eyes no okay you're you're rare Pisces without blue eyes that
look you but you have some fire in your chart i just like i you have like the fucking bull hair
you have like the airy skin you don't have the Pisces eyes i don't what's yours you know you're
What the fuck that means, okay, can I do your chart sometime behind the scenes?
Maybe if you don't know if you care probably don't want to be I'm gonna give your birthday or whatever. It's fine
But um, I just want to everybody knows everything about I was born February 28th. Oh
My god, that's like I think that's one of my grandpa's birthday. That's my grandpa actually
That's my grandfather's birthday, okay
Now I'm feeling now I'm like making some connections between my grandfather and you like how do you like golf?
Do you like watching golf or like really boring things like?
Do you like you want to be in you know, do you mute you mute commercials you hate commercials?
I can't honestly, I can't tell you the last time I watched TV like with
Yeah, yeah, exactly. Well, yeah, when you did would you mute the commercial? I mean, I just see like you're just like
No, I would just I was I'm a surfer man. I fucking just go channel to channel. I don't fuck with commercials
I I just go
Okay, you want your charge done amber contact me psyche a cult of psyche. Oh, I will I will do all that for you
Okay, Amber cos I key a cult of psyche calm
And also, you guys, I have a website called ColtCodex.me.
It has every one of my episodes.
It has every transcript.
I have all my videos private at the moment,
but every transcript is there.
You're all on there.
Everybody that's been on my show, even if you're mentioned in the show.
You're an IP grabber.
Don't trust it.
It's an IP grabber.
Q?
What?
Fuck you.
First of all, I don't do that shit.
Second of all, that's like a paranoid kind of thing and weird queue.
I'm just fucking with you. Relax.
Okay, okay. But as I don't say, don't don't even say that because people are paranoid in this community.
I don't, I made with cloud code. I don't care about your IP.
I seriously have no fucking interest in anybody's IP.
The thing is, if anybody really knew anything, your IP really doesn't even mean anything.
That's the whole thing, but people are paranoid.
Arthur, do you want to come up here?
Arthur, come on up.
Your IP changes like every 60 seconds or something.
Yeah, or use a VPN if you don't trust it.
There's no sign up.
There's no, there's no cost to anything.
All and you're on people.
Everyone's on there here.
Everybody's on there.
You just have to show a picture of your butthole to sign up.
Yeah, that's that's exactly that's and they're all personally confirmed by psyche himself
I am the butthole master. Okay, let me just say and I'm not even if it's a woman's butthole. I
Don't care. I don't care. They're all the same to me. Oh, you don't care. So you'd fuck a woman's butthole. I
Never have but the right woman a
Woman that was manly or a woman that was feminine
Probably like a like a gorgeous hot woman because I've already been with like an ogre and I'm done with that
I mean, it's like like I have my ex-girlfriend was like 55 years old
She was like 250 pounds and I never looked at her butthole nor her vagina
But I did put my finger in there and I made Niagara Falls reappear in my house
Hello, hello, all right, bud. Hey
I, I have legitimacy.
Well, Samman, why are you making that face, Samman?
Samman's making a frowning face.
And then-
You got work in the morning, right Sam and oh wait. No, you don't work
And it's literally under house arrest. He can't leave his house. That's why he's screams
Oh, he's just out here and pretends like he got a job, but he all he does all day
He's either on panel Instagram group chats
Discord all day long. When do you got time to work? No, no
Sam and
If you wanna come up here again,
I'm gonna need a picture of your butthole, okay?
And that's all there is to it, okay?
It's, I'm done.
I'm done with this bullshit.
I need a picture of your butthole.
Just for our coverage, I'll never show it.
I'll just look at it privately.
I promise you.
Okay, deal?
Okay, okay, okay.
Yeah, time out.
I mean, if you really wanna talk about fucking...
No, I'll hold you down and fucking yeah, please stick my dick
Okay, well cute you promise
Not you. Oh my god, this guy. Yo, you go door to door nigga. What's your job door to door?
All rapier door. Hey, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
He's just 430 in the morning.
Mr. Oh, I got a job.
I got a job.
Dude, I never swimmed in a drink, nigga.
You know that.
That's all you do is cry.
You can sit up here.
You can sit up here alone with Psyche.
Yeah, you can sit up here alone with Psyche.
What's your problem?
You being gay?
I don't like talking to you, nigga.
I don't like talking to you.
You're annoying.
Shut my face.
You fucking Psyche, nigga.
You with a faggot anyway?
Damn it, can I?
What the fuck?
Pack yourself up, nigga.
Pack yourself up, bitch-ass nigga.
Pack it up.
Take over, nigga, what up, man, bud?
What the fuck?
Can I do it?
All right, nigga, you good?
Okay, I'm gonna do it right now.
This is my time, baby
What he'd say on one his morning on beautiful
He's scared and but you know he's scared of me
Pack them up
What what what website you got your money? I'm gonna get I'm gonna pack it in salmon
No, you got you got your McDonald's America. I did. I had my fries. I had a cheeseburger
My like six cigars I had a perfect day
Look at that. Look at that lame ziggy. That thing is the lame jiggies are other lame jiggy. This jiggy
Ziggy Ziggy Ziggy
Can you sing that?
Sing getting zicky with it, please?
I'm your momo-ass.
I'm not a momo, man.
You want to go to a momo?
It means motel room.
And we can go to a momo.
Yo, the temperature, yo, it was like 80-something drop today.
God damn, today's going to be cold.
Best night in the world.
Hold on, this is the best night in the world.
Santa, I'm having the best night in the world.
Is it 430?
Man, wow, wow, Q, why you got to mention kids?
Yo, you're being weird, man.
Stop being weird, man.
Stop being weird.
I'm like door to door, door to door.
Hey, door to door.
What's up, door to door to door, nigga?
Try to dox my job.
You can go to another door?
I know you ain't crying to
fight.
House arrest.
That's the door to door.
Hey, what are you doing, bro?
What are you doing, brother?
How are you doing, bro?
Don't see me as my big brother.
I don't fuck with you nigga. Hey, I fuck with you. What are you talking about?
What are you talking about? What do you mean? I don't know what you're talking about.
What are you doing? What are you doing saying man? I love you brother. Ziggy you're a weirdo.
Hey, bro, you keep calling me a weirdo when you being a weirdo and fucking be done and all that kind of shit, bro
The best
Your e-girlfriend is a old bitch
That's a JT nigga you
Another brother from another mother nigga, I'm not your brother nigga
Okay, okay, when you're gonna come to New York and give me some
New York and give me some pussy
Okay, man, well, hey, girl, action is crazy!
I'm gonna do a twenty-first time in the stream.
I'll talk to you, niggas, you smell like shit, nigga.
That's why I never go to the door, nigga.
Do your door to door, nigga.
You not making money, nigga.
You're not going to sell drugs, sir.
I'm going to get it.
You're not going to sell drugs, nigga.
Door to door.
Go do your door to door, nigga.
Hurry up.
Yeah, I just came at work with them,
and right there, where are you sitting,
and who's that on the top right of the screen?
Yeah, there ain't no doctors.
Oh, my God.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
When you go to New York and give me some
We'll have a queue you can wash up
You don't know how to wash
Yeah, nigga, you're up your homer-ass nigga
Sam, look at the screen. Have you seen that one?
Begging for pussy. Please come to New York, please.
Please remember faking for pussy bruh that nigga is sad bruh that nigga is sad
If you remember you in in the beginning
No I'm blabbering
And you didn't blab potions
Super sad
My heart is left you nigga
Tizzy that nigga is sad
Tizzy I heard of Black KK you didn't blab potions
Please I need please I live in this city full of fucking three
30 million people, please KK come to New York and give me some pussy cuz I can't find none in fucking New York
How many fucking women are in New York City? I can't get no pussy here
Hockey's why you said I smell like shit
For me because I fuck with me
She said you stink!
She said you stink nigga!
That's just crazy nigga!
Same man in the beginning, you stink watch your ass, nigga, good job, now let's go to the door, go to the door, nigga, we not seeing you, you do the door to door, nigga, good job, let's go to the door, you fucking faggot ass, nigga, you done it.
This is called getting cut the way, this is called getting cut.
This is called getting cut.
Yeah, he was nice in the beginning, but then now and now I was like Bina and that was like another person I know they were nice in the beginning.
Yeah, exactly.
That's a man and you got a little yellow warm right here on your shit psyche.
Dumb you
Fuck you up
Your best friend
Smite shit nigga, pack yourself up.
Then pedophiles usually hang around with other pedophiles, just saying.
Best friend.
Just throwing that out there.
Best friend, man.
You said, you said you wanted a great kid.
You did.
Have you ever had a fucking thought in your life that nobody else could think of?
Have you ever had like a real, like a, have you ever had like a, an expansive thought that, like, oh man, maybe Samman added something to the equation, something to the conversation that nobody else could think of?
No, that's never happened. All you do is make noises and say the same three things over and over again.
You make noises, you say the same three things over again, you play with you, you have parts, you get notes, you see, I fucking stab you in the neck and you do nothing about it.
I was trying to say you want to rape people, man. What's up with you and rapes, bro? What's up with you and raping people, bro?
It's funny, though.
She on the other side on T.
No, I rape you, boy.
I see you on the other side.
Yeah, baby.
I see you on the other side on T.
I'm gonna see you on the other side, Torres.
And I'm a senior and Joseph, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina, I'm a senior and Josephina
My family's there for the drug addicts.
It ain't different.
It ain't different, my nigga.
Don't mad at me.
Don't mad and cry at me about shit that happened to you three years ago, you fucking cry, baby.
That's all you do is fucking cry. You enjoy panels all day and fucking cry. Your entire life is sitting on YouTube and crying and got to being like a fucking 40 year old white woman at your whole life.
You live your entire life as a 40 year old white woman crying on YouTube. That's all you are. That's all you are, boy.
You got some money for me.
That's all you are, boy.
That's what you said to me, nigga.
Ask me some money for me, nigga.
That's all you are, boy.
That's all you'll ever be, boy.
Go support yourself, nigga.
Door to door.
Ha ha ha ha.
Go to door, nigga.
Go to door to door, nigga.
Go make that brand, nigga.
We're good over here. You're not. You're not making moves. We're good. We're good over here. Sit on this for all day, Papa. Yeah, I never extra bread. Never. You never sit on this for it all day, Papa. Yeah, yeah, you do. All day. Sit on this court all day, Papa.
Like a lazy mother fucker.
You never see me break for money, nigga.
That's you and Big T, nigga.
That's a hundred.
Oh, I've seen you beg for money plenty
Yo, I need weed can I give me some money? That's you in big team. They good. That's not me
Always begging for bread. I'll stay with the pack. Please send me a hundred dollars. I'll kick myself from the panel if you send me a hundred dollars
I'll kick myself from the panel if you send me a hundred dollars
Because you know how many niggas don't like you.
So it's like, yeah, they'll send you $100 just to get you off the road.
That's not begging.
That's the system.
Remember, you should do the capture stuff.
Yeah, that's begging.
Oh, send me $100 and I'll leave my own panel.
Oh, yeah.
I can do the capture.
He actually donned it, too.
He actually donned it.
He actually leaves.
Hey, trust you nigga remember remember you did the class systems to begs
Easy-clap money
Hey psyche
There's my girl Amber remember with you with somebody Amber. He's a doc
A hit different you got a job
Thank you, it's never gonna go anywhere if you let him talk
Any of us think any of us is like perfect like we've all done fucked up shit
You're wrong Samman is actually perfect you're wrong
Thank you God bless America.
Say man's never done anything wrong.
Say man's definitely didn't go to prison.
Say man definitely didn't go to prison.
Why are you screaming?
Why are you screaming nigga?
Definitely never went to prison.
I was in prison. I was in prison.
I was in prison. I was in prison. I was in prison. I was in prison. I was in prison.
I was in prison. I was in prison. I was in prison.
I was in prison. I was in prison.
I don't want to go to jail.
I know I didn't shave my legs the entire time I was there.
It's a cool thing to go to jail, but us white people don't think the same.
No, no, no, I didn't know it was cool to be in a tent with a nigger.
I know it's cool for fucking blacks and brown people like you to go to jail.
It's like a badge of honor, but white people don't think the same way.
Sorry.
You slept in a tent.
You was homeless.
White people don't think the same way that you do, boy.
I know.
You know what's crazy?
You know what's crazy about that?
I was
Right, you know same in here
I was sleeping in a tent. I was sleeping in a tent six months ago and six months later
I have the same amount of shit in my life that you do nothing
I never said the same thing that you do nothing. I don't have a car. I don't have
You
Buddy, we're the same level. What do you have a couple pairs of Jordans?
You got a couple pairs of Jordans you think you're winning because you got a couple pairs of Jordans
You have the same thing that I have
You don't have a house, you don't have a car
You don't have a fucking family
You ain't the same, same
We're in the same boat there Sammy
I don't have a brother or sister to actually fuck with you
No, I'm talking about a family like a wife and children, not brothers and sisters.
I'm talking about a family, family.
I'm talking about a family that a man creates, not a family that you're born to.
Can I just say that I have that?
Oh, your brother.
Don't forget that.
You have the same thing that I have saying that, nothing.
You don't have a car, you don't have a couch, you don't have a family,
you don't have a wife, you don't have nothing just to do.
So why do you plan to do the same thing that I do?
Can I say how I know that yeah, I have that I can flex
Family
You're being a weirdo that much hurt my nigga. That much hurt. I feel you. I'm
My sister would hate me for being a weirdo, I hate myself too
Nobody likes you, bro. Literally nobody likes you. Why do you even come around here nigga? Nobody likes you
Nobody
I like salmon. Yeah, you let anybody who's your friend because it's hard for you to find friends. I understand
Especially off the internet and that's what I'm talking about
I'm sure you do. I'm sure you're just a fucking social butterfly, Amber. I'm sure you are
That's exactly what Amber is talking about
That's her daily, you know
Amber sober
I am a social butterfly
Thank you Amber
Amber Amber
People yeah, and a family
Yeah
Wait, Sam, man, are you sober?
Amber, Amber, you never slept in a tent.
Amber, you're Sam, man, are you sober?
Kumbaya, my lord.
I've never lived in a tent.
Sam, man, can't go five seconds without smoking a blood,
but he's, yeah, he's sober, right?
OK.
Yeah, I love weed, nigga.
I hate it.
Yeah, you live here so fast.
You live here so fast.
You can't even exist.
You can't exist on this earth without weed.
You're like what the fuck I'm not smoking a blunt right now. What am I even?
Your brain doesn't even know how to
Fuck
Yeah, you need that. You need that. That's good for you, buddy. You need that little nickel. Well, you need a
You need that, buddy. You need that
You pay a hundred and twenty dollars for a fucking quarter of spray pack in new york, okay
Fucking 30 bucks for a half ounce. Fuck. It's a whole different world out here, boy
You have the whole different world out here, boy. Who's up here for weeks the whole different world out here, boy
Oh, I know I know yeah, I know Sam and you're so cool. You get your weed for free, right?
We say people we you're so cool. You get your weed for free, right?
If only you're if only osempic when it came out before your mother died
I need you might still be alive fucking cute
Talking to you. I don't hurt me. You know why?
They don't hurt me.
My family's down for the drug addicts, my nigga.
God bless you.
No, man.
No, they're all just addicted to food.
They're all just addicted to food.
I feel a dragon coming.
Shout to the food, man.
God bless America with food, man.
God bless America.
You're a drug addict, nigga.
That's it.
Yeah, you are.
Yeah, you're a drug addict.
I mean, most of you guys, I mean, most of the people on panel are.
I didn't even say that, I just want to be big.
1-2-4-5, good.
I knew there was five people on panel, I was wondering what happened here.
Mm-hmm. No Q it gets mad. It's funny that Q lost his parents you want to talk about my dad mom
You lost your parents you want to talk about my dad mom it's hilarious
Hey
What are you doing you turned on me you turned on me
Cornball
Do you not still have your fucking discord shit, yeah, I do I just don't have it on my computer, so I'll check it out
I don't
No, he's a fucking corn ball. He's a fucking idiot, dude.
Oh, Sam-Man battling everybody. Who do you battle anymore?
What is it?
My dick in your mouth, nigga.
Yeah, what do you do?
What did you say, Sam-Man? I like that. What did you say?
What does he battle?
You're saying that to me?
What does Sam-Man battle anymore?
Hello nothing
You don't
Yo, hey, this one. They just got to get off the panel like that Rambo remember that
Come on man, it's probably lost service or something shut up wait till he comes back
You just stop dick sucking my niggas
Wait a minute though, cuz I need to clarify something with midnight like midnight
I'm not saying I'm not gonna say that's a man's hypocritical. Yes. Sometimes he does
But listen listen listen, I don't give a fuck about men. Yes, but I want to clarify something to just hear me out
Don't know man. I she's a cake goon
I'm not saying
She's been
45 I'm just saying you didn't for two seconds same man. That's all he has it. We don't we don't need to mute him
Q45 brought up the family first is all I was gonna say
Yeah, what did I got our magic given the fuck one cute?
My family's not full of drug addicts. Like I said, nigga
The fuck
What does that mean? I don't know what you're talking about is that me came up on you stupid nigga fuck you stupid
Fuck you fuck whatever I get it though. Hey, man, you know, you know, I'll get I'll get you you know, I'll get you back always
I'm not I love everybody like I don't like I really only hate Ron at this
You don't love everybody be quiet. Oh
Yeah, I have no idea midnight
I'm just saying that's all I was saying is like you 45 brought it up first
And I miss a lot of this shit like and that's why I go where I want and I do what I want because I don't follow a lot of the
Fucking drama
I don't care man. I go to cake go anywhere. I don't
Did you hear what Ziggy just said? I told you. I told you midnight. Did you hear what Ziggy just said?
I fucking told you. I said mark my words
Did you hear what he said midnight and no they didn't hear
Yeah, but did you hear what Ziggy just said?
Did you say because I'm not to a lot of people I told you I said mark my words
I'm gonna go up there and do you's gonna turn it into how I'm a snitch and then I just said
I love everybody and I can't follow all this shit and
People I fucking told you I told you
Look even though you know the most beautiful thing I ever saw was her singing. It was good. Oh, thank you
It was I saw you in the bar
Know a lot of people tell me I should go on
No, no, it it turned me off, but that's like I saw are doing it and
That's when me and you first met remember that you yes large. That's BG
Fuck yeah minute
Manette
I can't really sing right now. I have to be quiet.
Then when he did that, I was like, oh, fuck!
I told you, Midnight. I told you, Midnight.
I said, I said, I said, I said, Midnight, I'm gonna join in a little bit and mark my words,
no matter what the conversation is, Ziggy's gonna turn into how I'm a snitch.
I said, Ziggy's gonna turn into how I'm a snitch.
It's all right. I don't like that. So it's my exactly RG. Thank you
I have said and done some fucked up shit
But all's I know is I have turned my shit around
I've made priorities like I put my priorities in order
And like so I'm laying that hard for me in forever. Like what are you doing now?
That's why you haven't heard from me forever is because my life like my real life shit's more important than internet shit
Like yesterday, I spent four and a half hours at the fair with my son.
That's cool.
My body fucking hurts.
She said her body hurts.
Okay, now I believe her.
My body fucking hurts.
I'm old as fuck, bro.
Candy bars, deep fried stickers, I would like those.
Thank you, Manette.
The what?
Deep fried stickers.
Manette's very beautiful.
That's not like that kind of fair.
They don't have all that fancy shit, like.
But that would be cool if they had that hair,
but it's just like the normal state fair.
At the Juggalos, they have deep fried
Fego soda and hot dogs and stuff.
I had to take a call.
Deep fried what?
Hot dogs and Fego.
Oh, there was! I saw something like in the grape, the grape-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'-fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuckin'fuck
They're very you have to show your beholder say hi. That's literally how they greet each other. Mm-hmm
No, that's not how they greet each other
Jimmy loves me when I'm on panel. I don't give fuck
I'm on panel site
What up, Emma Erickson? Good, Amber?
I'm about to dip out to the floor.
I want to see Black Tits.
Everything's good, yes, Samman.
Everything's good.
See what he said?
Hey, wait, I want to see Black Tits.
No, he did not say that he said I'm about to dip out after this blunt
Come up here, come up here and cook Sam in for me, I want to eat him after the show.
What's up with you?
What's up with you being gay on me?
Can I get where everybody else, man?
What do you mean?
What's up with you being gay with me, you fucking momo-ass nigga?
Fuck it. He's a fucking idiot.
What's momo?
You already know him.
I will.
He's just being annoying.
You mean the motel room, right?
No, it's not being momo, man.
What's momo? What's momo mean?
a detestable person that momo shed you don't know I've never heard that but I
you know what I think of is that character Momo you know like the big
white guy that's exactly what oh momo you have yeah it looks like it
yeah now you want to go to sleep look look go she she she's
Who who mr. Dr. Himself now he crying
W nigga, I would never do that nigga. I brought the I rather hustle crack nigga
They sleep with a nigga in the tech nigga. I'd rather not be you
Hey, I never I mean lots of people live in tents. I'm not gonna hit
Cook that stir fry let's go
Yeah, he's a crack on you. We'll never forget
Guys, we have a special guest tonight
No
Morning
I'm so glad it's not Arthur. I'm so glad it's Arthur. It is Arthur. It is Arthur. Hey, he's Seiki. How are you?
Yeah, but Arthur
The panel, how are you?
You're on
Arthur, how come you've never gotten an impersonation of me? I'd like you to do an impersonation of me because you're a fucking fat bitch
So, you do impersonations only of people you like?
I don't understand.
It's just you would seek attention everywhere.
Can I get a wrench please?
I want to confirm it's me.
I don't want to.
I'm not. I'm not. I'm not.
I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm
I'll see your mother in hell, Samman.
You want to rape the dead?
That's your crazy, man, nigga.
You're a weirdo.
Exactly.
You can come to this niggard, too.
Bye, guys.
Good luck, guys.
God damn.
God bless America.
You're a weirdo.
Hey, guys.
But can I?
I need to say one thing.
Arthur bitches that I cry about wrenching all the time, but every time he sees me have a wrench
He cries that I have a wrench and he doesn't so what does that say by relieving Samuel Torres?
Well
No, he ain't gonna leave
When I'm here when when Q's here
When I'm here, he ain't gonna leave. I'll keep this nigga on panel all night
I'll keep this nigga on panel all night
When I'm here, he is here. When I'm here, he is here. Trust me. When Q is here, then man is here
He is on my dick. He is all over my Johnson
You lost it. He is all over my
as long as Q is here, Sandman is
here. You can just you can
you're all night Sandman. It's
okay, buddy. Pack you up. Pack
you up. Send me. Send me.
What happened? You lost your
heirloom. He got mad. I'm going
to see Josephina in hell. Do
you like this? Oh my god.
You hurt me.
I would like someone I would like someone I really would like someone to do an impersonation of me
Like do I not have like a character that it's like easy to yes. Yes. I can do it
Do it do it. I can do it. Oh my gosh really arrested right now
Oh my god, that's not even a second. That's stupid
That's fucking stupid
Well, can I please have my bait bait or like
This ain't an alcoholic just the alcohol you're stupid ziggie you're fucking stupid
Arthur's characters are at least funny like what the arse there? Can you do impersonation of me, please?
We're out of here like 15 minutes ago you ain't going nowhere
Man you ain't going nowhere you're stuck here man. You ain't going nowhere boy
Stay man. You're stuck here boy. You can't leave. You thought you could stay man
You thought you could leave without me telling you that you could leave
This is Marine Boot Camp Negro, Marine Boot Camp Negro.
That's what I'm talking about.
My man said he had to take a bus.
You thought you could just leave this panel without me giving you the fucking clearance?
You thought that you could just leave this panel without me giving you the clearance?
No, you ain't not, you ain't allowed to leave, dammit.
And that's how you get him to leave.
That's how you get him to leave.
That's exactly how you get him to leave right there.
The fucking goddamn face and the goddamn shit, dude.
All up in the face.
That's exactly how you get that motherfucker to leave.
Don't hate me, Q.
I don't know about hate but I still smack this shit out of you and we can
do what you do the flat boxing contest that'd be fun
And I'm just you know, I've actually I actually slapped you before so I don't know
No, no, no, I'm talking about in John's kitchen before we went to the bar
No, wait, wait, wait, no, no, no diggies
Wait, stroke off. You don't remember in John's kitchen before we went to the bar, before we went outside. You don't remember.
Probably pretty fucking already drunk by that point.
You stood there with your hands behind your back and you said slap me as hard as you can.
Did I?
Yeah, you don't remember that fucking shit then fucking you slapped me. I don't give a fuck cool
Slapped it out of your memory too
Fucking memories memory did fucking that shit
Believe it's Mike. I still have fucking your and fucking Crystal Marie shit
Like I have you from what is it? I
Honestly
Ziggy is the Ziggies gay just don't
Yeah, give Ziggy no, he went he went to
Strawberry farms or something and I'm the one that fucking like got him
Yeah
Yeah, I know you're also the one that introduced ice Poseidon to IRL streaming. Are you talking about kiwi farms?
Key, you know, it's not kiwi farms. What's the strawberry farm sounds like a fucking porn site?
I don't know what the hell. I've never been there. He went to fucking something
Farms, and then he was like he got in trouble at the fucking farms Mike
elaborate
The biggest problem is that he hasn't had his doughnut whole rated
Don't know man. It's something. I get it for you
Fucking on camera and whatever and I made videos and he even asked him I was like man, is it cool I get he's like
He's like, yeah, I don't do I give a fuck about anything. Do I really? Yeah, no
Don't have much to give a fuck
You know you're pretty cool about it cuz I was like don't have to do it like a license or anything
You're like nope
Hey
Listen nigga is he leaves the panel and then he comes into chat and he's like saying goodbye everybody goodbye everybody like listen
Nobody cares just just leave like you're not that important bro like
I'm kind of a big deal that's like a weird. That's like that's like imagine imagine leaving somebody's house
Imagine walking out the same goodbye to somebody walking out of their house
Then opening up the door again walking back in and saying goodbye and then walking back out the door again
Something Barry farms
Were you he got in trouble? Do you remember that not very not very far
Yeah, I was fucking walking on the flame
Our sir quit timing out like a little bitch
Then the homie gave my the security guard my name bro didn't try to ban me for five years
You got some awesome hair
Thanks, man
I see. Amber, this shows you're barely around here.
Psychey and I have spoken because because Sam
Alex to make money off of us, we're going to help them out.
And we'll every time he gets done, we'll just time them out back.
Yeah, I agree with that.
You know, every time you can shout Arthur, you have no content.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
So explain to me how does he make money? Arthur's not a streamer. Yeah. How does he make money off? No Arthur, you explain
He's made money off of you. He's made money off of you Amber. Are you kidding me?
Exactly. Yeah, it's because I'm content but what kind of money is he made off of Arthur?
How many times how many times have people how many times have people paid to clap Arthur off his banner? Exactly!
OK, that's true.
But that's because we don't like Arthur.
It's nothing to do with psyche.
OK, well, it's still making money off of Arthur.
But regardless of how it's made, it's still making money off of him.
OK, but Arthur is timing out like a little bitch.
They're timing out like a little bitch.
Thank you, and I have already spoken about this.
Shut the fuck up. OK, well, you're timing out like a little bitch.
Shut the fuck up.
a little bitch a little bitch a little bitch well she's a she's oblivion to
everything you know that's all she always has been oblivious I'm oblivious
to me no I'm not okay I'm not a TV thing so maybe I had no you're talking
about like the Elder Scrolls game
Gotta say this your self-awareness sucks because you got pop, bro, and you fucking could have got away dude
I do just hop in that car and drive
It wouldn't have found
Have a way
There's that fucking scribbles faggot
who
Remember, bro, I saw the video didn't she got pop? Oh my god, bro
Hardcore criminals, you know
I know Mike, but I was too much of a pussy man. I mean you can't own a gun
You can't own a gun. I can't I got my rights. You're a felon
I got my rights back, you dumbass.
How?
How did you get an expunge?
It ain't been five years.
It ain't even been fucking two years.
You don't have to.
It's called, because of the level of felonitis, it was a, it was a classics felony, and so
I was able to get my chart set aside, and right now I'm in the process of getting my
rights back.
Oh
Okay, so hold your horses there, ma'am
You have been in the process of getting clean how many times
Oh man, it might take a few attempts, might take a few attempts, but okay to answer your
question to the extent and the mentality of getting clean that I am right now never like
this is the first time I've been like ready to do it and wanting to come on to that.
Yeah, you have a blueprint on the side finally.
What?
Wow.
Wow, why do you why do you got to make shit up like that?
No, so like before you got with your main dude at the time. Do you know who I'm talking about?
I was like, I'm not wow she ziggy
She seems so good and then you got in trouble
Avocado Mike, I'm just Ziggy stop you're just gonna turn this into me being a snitch and how you love me
And it's the same thing so we're not gonna go
No, Mike, I just want to know what you're gonna fucking parking lot
Oh, okay. Yeah, I know what stress you're talking about.
Oh, yeah, that was the Darth Vader bong one.
No, are you talking about?
No, that was the first one.
No, he's talking about the one with all the Mexicans.
No, that wasn't the parking lot, the parking lot one was the Darth Vader one.
Well, there was two parking lot ones, but okay.
Listen Amber, I have actually watched these a rep can put it just multiple times and you've never watched any of them.
So I think I remember going around the bunch of Mexicans.
Jesus, but Mike the one where you were in the parking lot of where you fucking where he was like
Oh, I saw you pulling out of a notorious fentanyl dealers house that
And it was like a food food card or something. Yeah, he sent you to the store with his EBT card or whatever
Hey guys, guess what what and we're
What I don't gauge
Gates, yeah, we're two meter. How long have you known her?
What's after midnight? How long has she been over 18?
He's 40 or 41
This got money. Oh, wow, you finally found one in your fucking age range
Maybe next time I see you I won't slam you
Is that who you're with right now my wife will probably kick your ass, bro
She's 41 years old a little bitch. She's got some fucking guns, bro. She doesn't
Are you with her right now? Is that her?
He looks scared. Yes, that must be her
Can we see her?
He hit the mute button without even looking
No, bro, it's not muted. I can hear him. It's not muted
There's people sleeping in this house. I'm in a fucking house. He was like a lot of people do you?
She told me shouldn't fuck up. I have to do my inside voice tonight. It's hard for me to mess with boys
I have a bad hearing a bad hearing who's sleeping in the house like a deaf person
Who's sleeping in the house? Nobody no
Okay, they're about to get divorced already bananas and peanut butter
Just whip your dick out. Yeah, is she is she eating it with fucking rice Krispies Coco Krispies? Hi
Hi, how are you? Is she eating her peanut butter and banana with Coco Krispies? That's not my favorite. Are you in a home for retarded people?
What the fuck?
Oh, hi homegirl.
That person looked like they were walking like a zombie.
God.
Why are you such a dick?
Can't you just embrace like the positivity of the situation?
I'm asking questions.
I'm a true crime.
I'm an investigative journalist.
Yeah, okay, you know my bitch my bitch drive a fucking 2026 fucking forerunner with like a laptop on the dash
But I was like what the hell where's she at? Why are you?
We just saw the shield me a yogurt
Nana's bread and peanut butter and honey
Is your bitch is sugar mama
Q's just getting weird
That's a little hazel right there. That dog is a woman at take it for a fucking walk
The dog is a fucking people bro. No, it's yeah, it's it's extremely fat
Definitely a people definitely
It's not a pit bull. She's got some pit bull. No, she's like a boxer. Oh, she might have some people shit people
No, I kind of look like a little shit to you. She used to work. She used to work for she was a vet techer for years
There's like a shit to you. Oh, one of the one of the surgeons fucking took her in and she took her home
You know this chick right here? Yeah, she's the she's the one or like the the the vet techs like scalpel
She'd run up at the scalpel and he's like
Well, I hope you guys didn't do like, you know life insurance the shit. Yeah, she came up
Talking about animals, bro. This dog's a fucking seal bro. The thing will fucking drag its back legs and flop its front legs
This fucking dogs a seal
Like you said she's older
Yeah, she's like fucking she's older. She's up. She's over a decade for sure. Probably like 14
So yeah, she's like 12 13
Anybody join an airport mom
No
What does this guy do
He's laying down
If you don't let him join like he is a like he is a cat trafficker
God
You found some 19-year-olds on the way there and got distracted will your friend will your friend join the panel
I meant my
That air air bring your friend on the panel. Let's talk to your friend. Let's see. We
Yeah, no, oh so she has a beard too
I'm a twin too. I have a twin sister
Really? Oh, we know
Sister your twin sister looks even more like the thing than you do
Stop saying that about my sister
She's scary
My twin is a bigger based in we're fraternal
I saw my sister three years ago is she taller or shorter
She's probably different size now. It's been three years. We're both we're both fat
Actually, she's better than me. No, I know he's right. There's a fat. There's a fat and skinny one
She is fatter than me. Yes. Yeah, but okay. You're the singer and what does she do and play the drum?
She does not sing. No, um, I'm right-handed. She's left-handed. I'm blonde. She's Burnett
Weird. Yeah, I know she would not have an only fan
Oh, wait, no, you both
She has
You both went to jail
Actually, I smoke mess way longer than hers. She only did it for like a year and a half
Did you get your sister hooked on math?
No, guys, she was dating our have you ever smoke the metal?
He's asking at one point. I appreciate your honesty
At one point whenever you guys
You were like, yeah, that is awesome
Cause if you said no, I wouldn't have believed you because it's like, obviously like, I mean, I've, I've smoked weed with my brother when I was like 16, you know what I mean? Like, so obviously if you do the same drugs, you're gonna fucking, you're gonna smoke them together.
We didn't do it. I mean, dude, I smoked weed with my mom.
Don't say her name. Don't say her name. Please do not say her name.
I'm not gonna say names of relatives, please. I didn't say I wasn't even about to say anything
No, I know you went but Ziggy asked her name and I
Didn't even hear I don't even I don't even listen to Ziggy. He's just like background
I was like wait, I wasn't
You guys are in your little bubbles and psyches over here fucking the lessons cat
He would never look at all you would not
Dude, what are you doing?
I mean, I
Girl, I don't want to hear nothing about molestation and you're only like four inches away from that dog's butthole, so
I'm not doing I'm like fucking up like
five feet away. Hey, I want I want to say, uh, you guys
are here. But later. Who said, take care. Take care,
dog. Have fun with my fucking Barry Fawn videos.
Oh, what's going on here?
They're gone. Don't worry about it.
Mike, you're banned from the Inland Empire.
I hope you know that.
You're banned from the Inland Empire.
If I catch you in the IE again,
I'm fucking you up.
You talking to me, bro?
Yeah, you're banned from the Inland Empire.
Okay, buddy.
You're banned from here. You're not allowed here.
You're not allowed to stream here anymore.
You're done.
What's the Inland Empire?
The Inland Empire is like everything that's east of Los Angeles before you hit Vegas.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Right here.
It's all good.
Hey, bro, we could be chill bro. Like fucking you out of your little beef, bro
You got your little donations. I'm just fucking with you and you're getting all dorky about no
Yeah, Q45 does not get on fire
No, I think I'll still wander me into part of the earth I want
Me and Q45 used to be really close and now we're like, I don't know what to call it
Yeah, front of me is yeah, I
Like that box
It does suck. He hurt me. He hurt me really bad
No, and now here we are and I mean, I mean, you know people people's driving for something to talk about
Good and they fucking stress on fucking other people's fucking trauma
which is sad but it is what it is but it's our fault for putting like what is
our fault for putting that trauma on what is that lots of yeah what's your
trauma
Lots too much. Oh
What the the decks break your heart that much see there you go, dude
There you go. No, that's not that's not not even a blip in the radar, bro
What are you talking about not even a blip?
You both on Benny's and you were like about to kill me cuz I was like talking to Dex. I'm yes. Yes, exactly him
Dex
How about this
I don't mention her name.
Mike was like, damn, I can't find somebody who's like,
even within 12 years of my age range.
So I got to go find somebody who's vulnerable.
I got to go find somebody who's like vulnerable
and who's like easily manipulated 19 years old, teen, teen, teen, years old.
Is you react to that?
He's the second time you got fucking sidewalk slammed, bro.
I told you that show was going to happen before I met you.
And I told John why that's why that's why when you see me you were like all shit. Here we go
No, I told John that didn't guess what I did bro. I ubered you to the bar
Back from the bar. I know I used you to buy me some drinks for the night. And when we got back, I fucked you up
Bro, you know what punk means do when you're in jail, bro
No, you got punked I used you and made you pay for all the drinks made you pay for the ubers
I didn't get we got back there. I fucking disrespected you and put you on your ass. That's what happened
Oh, you grabbed my backpack strap. Good for you, bud
What a fucking what a fucking great fucking human and what did you do? You didn't fucking face to face me
And what did you do? What did you do? So somebody disrespects you and fucking me slams you to the ground by your backpack
And what did you do in return?
Nothing not a thing. Mike. I'm just curious
Mike, I'm just curious why you even care about being like on good terms with Q45
Don't I just saying I was good. I wouldn't I didn't back down. I'll tell him he's saying that I was a little bit
Exactly. I mean, do I do I look like I'm sitting here trying to be on good terms with him? Like I don't give a fuck about this
I would do this a I don't have no regrets about that situation. I would do the same thing every single chance
Don't let Arthur time him out. Don't fucking time out Arthur. I'm gonna fuck up fine, June. I'm gonna
Pee in your butt.
Just time them out for 10 seconds.
So, you know, it just releases comments.
Just keep telling them out for 10 seconds.
That's all.
Because it's only 10 seconds who cares it's kind of so fucking annoying exactly. Thank you psyche
That's what a noisy. I don't care about a noisy man. Sam has me exactly just annoying him
It's not he like he'll be back tomorrow. He comes back every day
Yeah, I mean you can
Dog and he'll come back
a psyche you could have the same like I don't want to say like grift but same
concept of like having people kicked off your piano for $25
$2 off of like you know okay yeah okay so we can't get mad at him or Amber he
will have my content playing and then I'll come up and they start a fight with
beta and it'll be like great and then he'll stop stop it'll get me kicked off
Troll of doing her lip liner for the next five hours
Why don't you recap salmon then I can look like some mother fucker because Sam is content is recapping everybody else
Recapping everybody else
Recap recap salmon joining a pin just are you gonna have like a recap inception or something like what's the
or a recap Sam and joining a panel, because even if he has like my content that he can use, he'll still like learn to make a tutorial.
I like watch her do her island.
Oh yeah, I'm going to recap Sam and joining a panel and saying the same three things over and over and over.
Yeah, you're heard and you can talk to us and you're heard.
Oh my God.
You're heard, nigga.
Oh my God, nigga.
Oh my God.
I mean, you're recapping it right now.
Like you could do that.
I just know talking about people that fucking deserve to be talk shit on their fucking baggage. Yeah, I'm so mad
I'm so I'm so mad and hurt, you know, that's why I had never sugar exactly RG
Right, that's why I'm so mad and I still you on the panel
I still you talk your shit, and I'm still nice to you
You call me crackhead a faggot a nigger all the time and you mean man if I call you a nigger then all of a sudden
It's a scandal and he's a dirty nigger. Oh my god
Hey, I didn't say
I'm talking about vinegar like what you cook with like how you bake
Vinegar dirty vinegar
How we say it dirty even apple cider vinegar about that apple cider better. Oh, okay
That's a lot nicer, yeah.
So, K45.
I just say I'm going to say penalty hold and how I spell it, how he says it, I want to
say it.
Penalty?
Penalty.
He says penalty.
Oh, yeah.
What do you think of mine in BT?
Oh, yeah, that's the American education system failing once again.
Well
And imagine living in the fucking the most the biggest city on earth
You live in the big the biggest city in America and the education system in the biggest city in America has fucking failed you to the extent that you
Can't even put a fucking sentence together
Hey, this is out of context crazy
He didn't, because he's a huge car, he's a huge...
I'm just kidding, that was another joke.
Nope, it should have.
That's a Samman.
That's a Samman flip.
Mind you, mind you.
It's what, like, 5.30 in the morning in New York City?
Electric skateboarding took off and left me here and when he first joined the panel, it was like for something in the morning for him
So he wakes up in the morning and his first thought on his mind is let me go on psyche's panel and talk to Q45
Hey, if you say that again, you're gonna get a penity. Okay, cuz you're taking him out of a car. Thank you
You
Q
He's talking to you cute for five. I'm not getting a fucking yeah, nobody's talking. I'm waiting for him to fucking talk
Say what he's gonna say didn't respond back when I
Hate you. You're supposed to be like, I'm not sure fucking n-word n-word. Oh
my god
I was I was listening to you, but you want to say hey Q45. Hey Q45. Nobody was even talking
Why don't you just say what you're gonna say? He wanted to make sure that you were listening. Hey, thank you
Can I ask you a question? Hey, thank you. Can I ask you a question? Hey, thank you. Can I ask you a question?
The fuck no, there's not gonna have a conversation. Don't you know that?
Conversation where it's bro. You ask somebody. Hey, Q. You go. Hey, what's up? I mean acts you a question. That's what's there?
No, I'm retarded. Oh, so how much he doesn't know how to have a conversation. He's an asshole. All you guys do talk over each other
Anyway, yeah
Crazy panel. I don't have a talking stick. I just have a big I'll put it right up your butthole, boy
I'm ready for I'm ready for a cue. I'm bent over ready for you. He would like that. Yeah, I want it
Mike I'm not like trying to be an asshole to you. I'm just letting you know that he's an asshole like no
I know Amber. It's all good dude. You and me at least can have a back and forth
She responded
Yeah, we can
No, but Q45 is an asshole like I we already know this like listen the more that you
The world spins
Exactly, so the more that you expect any civility from Q45 you're not gonna get the only way that you have
70-something year-old man, it's very
Listen, I love my old man, bro.
Listen, Amber, you can love that old man all you want,
but the fact is, is that the average lifespan
for an American male is 83 years old.
You only got only a few more years.
Maybe if you're fucking lucky, you chose wrong.
You should have chose somebody that was younger
because you're not gonna have to deal with fucking burying.
No, he's gonna outlive me.
You're gonna have to bury that man.
You're going to have to bury that man one day and your feelings are all invested in it and it's going to be really bad for you and it's probably going to spiral you back into meth addiction.
Listen, Q. My family, most of the women on my grandmother's side have died from cancer around the age of 55.
I'm not talking about that. I'm talking about Sarge.
He's going to outlive me.
No, he's not
Watch yes, he is listen Amber. You're what 41 42 43
You're what oh
Okay, so you're 39 and Sarge is what Sarge is yours your spouse is what 71?
he just turned 72 yep okay so you're 39 and he's 72 you think you're gonna
outlive him you're fucking crazy
His parents lived till they were 91.
You're not gonna.
Oh, yeah.
He's got like five to 10 years tops.
But he's healthy, bro.
But listen, okay, on a serious note.
Listen, Q45, on a serious note.
You're gonna bury that, dude.
I'm sorry, you're gonna bury it.
He still doesn't take any medication.
He exercises every day.
He takes his vitamins.
He's healthy as fuck, bro.
Fucking what?
You know when bodies fall? Oh, yeah, they do
How many people have been healthy as fuck been athletes
Like are you kidding me? They'd be like 24 25 years old
Exactly and not gonna happen anybody
Listen, that's why love is love and age doesn't matter
Oh
You must have a lot of that's right
No, he doesn't what he does, but he's cheap as fuck. So that's why I work full time. You're the beneficiary. I'm sure I
Yeah, I'm yes
Yeah, so you're gonna fucking collect all that shit doing all his family members
For the benefit of some sort of stability in her life
Q you can vouch for this. It's not like he's rich rich. You've seen the house we rent
It's not a house. It's a fucking it's a shack. I'm surprised that you don't have a John Deere in that bitch
Have you checked Google Earth lately because it actually looks a lot better than it used to
Do you want me to check? Yes, check Google Earth and see what image is not I'd be honest with you
I really haven't in a long time. There's got to be a newer image in the one you've seen like those those things over the windows
Have been gone for like years. Listen Amber Amber. You better be careful. You better be fucking careful because
That's it. That shit better look like a fucking mansion
It doesn't look like a man just looks a lot better
If I look at it, you know, if it looks nice, I'll give you credit
It looks better. It's looks way better. We've painted it. We got different window covers over the windows
Can I say something come here ginger?
Yes, you love them if you love them. That's all that matters. I fucking love him
We still laugh every day
Like he gets me flowers like twice
He's a good dad, I love him so much
Quiet real quick. Let me talk. You're gonna have you're gonna have many more years after when he dies because he is gonna die very soon
He's not gonna last very long
And once he dies, you're gonna find love again, all right, I don't know
It's hard to find me to love that puts up with your flaws and like
Just do it again. Damn dude. We got cats. I mean, what's my fuck over here fucking
45 I thought I thought you were looking up the fucking Google Earth image
Yeah, we have one
Yeah, I can't do it on my phone either. I'm on my phone. Yeah, it's gotta go
Well, I gotta go I'm gonna go film some opossums do this bitch is taking care of like seven babies because their dog killed them the mom
Okay, he's gonna look up the image hopefully he'll be back
Okay, well Amber. Thank you for being on the show. Are you ending?
Yeah, I'm gonna go to I'm gonna go to sleepy bye, but you know what? Oh
Yeah, you know what? I'm gonna live a long time. You know why?
Why?
You know my motherfucking G. Bye
Okay, guys
Let me play something real quick and Mike stroke off your band from the show because you like to touch your
kids dick and
So just one more thing Amber, I love you
You know, go look at Robert Streisand's Google Earth image, by the way.
I think you really should.
And by the way, y'all motherfuckers aren't fooling me, okay?
Stroke up your nigger.
Stumbaya, Jalem Stumbaya, Sarva Jeeva Stumbaya, Sarva Krithyam Stumbaya, Sarva Roda Stumbaya, Sarva Jalem Stumbaya
Anni, the Jambilek, Sakalam, Adorathana, Sataya, Sataya, Devi, Tugam, Namaha, Boudhvi, Maha, Yogi, Di, Kauri, Om, Mata Swaha
Om Krishnobhassana Shattasahastra Goti Vadanasimhavahegi
Parvandhavra Parathandras Othani Sarvathustan
Bhaksaya Bhaksaya Sarvathadevana
Bandha Bandha Vithveshaya Vithveshaya Chwala Chikve
Mahabal Parakrama Pratyangire
Paravitya Chedini
Paramantranasini
Parayantra Phedini
Om True Namaha
You
in a mobile game.
I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't know what I'm saying, but I don't
Om Ksham Bhakshajwala Jigwe Karaladam Shre Kalarathri
trathhyangi re ksham phreem khum fat svaha
She wished for sin was a seed
She feeds on shit
The leaves turn red, and the night turns long.
She rises in shadows, fierce and strong.
Lilith in Scorpio, my anima flame,
whispers my secrets, calls out my name.
Just a tread with care
Your day-to-day covered with phase 44 super agents your life is chaotic
Yes you try, you misbehaving, feeding for lovers in brooms. Hands up for you, not a chance in the universe, you'll fail or lose, cause he's mine, always mine.